{
    "id": "dca2fe502d4f4ffcbb0904857a365f25",
    "title": "Gap Fills",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The new version is superior .................................. the old one.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "to",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "faf9a229dc9d4aaba606539c5e27a8bc"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is taller .................................. the other boys.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "then",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3fdfccda6046407eb8832d102b6bd71c"
        },
        {
            "question": "My job is to supervise people who are junior ................................. me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "cce871276e5f414198cc37beef200a2a"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is ......................................... most unique distinction.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f05b21fbe3f64e5597bb9daebd8cc83b"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is ....................................... good to be true.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6b6a7c31df904b7ca593be5c7522a213"
        },
        {
            "question": "My camera is .............................. than yours.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more good",
                "more better",
                "better"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "40c26acbe5b44ebfa54a48e71cb3fcc8"
        },
        {
            "question": "The master subjected the servant to the ................................... treatment.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "unkindest",
                "most unkindest",
                "most unkind"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4869e08ab7574db484fd2cc57596cd47"
        },
        {
            "question": "Ram is one of ....................... students in the class.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "best",
                "the best"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "31f5ed36b6d44c139cec279a88c5c602"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mr. Raman is ................................. member of the club.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "eldest",
                "oldest",
                "the oldest"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "110f181bccb74babb33349b3ae83cd74"
        },
        {
            "question": "Only two posts are senior ................................ mine.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9cda67fb167343fe8c8ce28fb72405d6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The matter had been discussed prior ............................ my arrival.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d9366129cf714c3d815311f83b5e32d9"
        }
    ]
}